=Born Again=
=Episode 16=
Alright.
That's enough.
Let's go.
Are you alright?
Let me see.
No. I'm fine.
Don't move.
You can't win, yet you came.
Well, I couldn't just watch them
all gang up on you.
So you just took the beating?
Did I hurt you?
I'm good.
Done.
Thanks.
Is your face okay?
It's nothing.
I should be thanking you.
You took that beating because of me.
You said you are my boyfriend.
I... I just said that to...
It's okay. I know.
Didn't expect you
to be so sharp back then.
How about I walk you home?
I'll walk you home.
Xiaotang, what happened to your face?
Nothing.
Get up, now.
Well, if it isn't
our class hero and beauty.
What? One night apart,
and your faces are all beat up?
Did you do something bad last night
and get cursed?
I bet they scratched each other.
Ye Shen,
felt good getting punched for someone
in that alley last night?
Of course.
And you.
Gu Xiaotang,
if it weren't for Ms. Lei last night,
you'd be in for it.
From now on, behave yourself.
Lin Wei, are you done?
Is bullying fun for you?
(Xia Na?)
(Look how desperately
you claw your way up,)
(it's truly disgusting.)
Xia Na, this is none of your business.
You treat Gu Xiaotang as a good friend,
but she's got a boyfriend now.
She doesn't have room for you anymore.
Gu Xiaotang,
if it weren't for Ms. Lei last night,
you'd be in for it.
From now on, behave yourself.
Should I hand this recording
of the time, place, people involved,
and the bullying over
to the homeroom teacher?
Let's go.
Xiaotang,
are you okay?
Xiaotang, what's wrong?
It's me, Xia Na.
(Yeah, at this time,
Xia Na hasn't turned bad yet.)
(She's still my best friend.)
(But something feels off.)
I'm fine.
I'll go to the restroom.
(She's being genuinely nice to me now.)
(I know.)
(But I just can't.)
(I can't just pretend nothing happened.)
Xiaotang, here.
Take it.
If you need this recording,
take it to the teacher anytime.
Lin Wei went too far.
We can't just let this slide.
Thank you.
Is there anything else?
No, that's all.
Then I'll
get going now.
Gu Xiaotang,
if it weren't for Ms. Lei last night,
you'd be in for it.
From now on, behave yourself.
Honey, what's going on?
- Did someone bully you?
- No, Mom.
Did Lin Wei bully you again?
- No.
- No?
What did you listen to?
Show it to me.
- No, Mom.
- Give it to me.
Mom, give it back.
What is this? Let me see.
- Give it back.
- It's proof Lin Wei bullied Xiaotang.
We need to see the teacher.
Lin Wei?
The contractor's daughter?
- Move! I haven't finished yet.
- Mom.
Come here.
It's her, right?
Su Dawei! Have you no shame?
This is proof
of someone bullying my daughter.
Are you going to use it to get money?
Proof?
School?
Bah!
Can the school give you money?
You think I raise you for free?
You got beaten up,
so you gotta make something back.
So what if you got beaten up?
If you don't use this evidence
to get me money,
are you saving it for your own funeral?
Su Dawei, have you lost your conscience?
You chose this path yourself.
So what if I chose it?
Listen carefully.
Next time you get bullied,
be smarter.
Record it clearer.
This is way faster
than you working for money.
Gu Xiaotang,
if it weren't for Ms. Lei last night,
you'd be in for it.
From now on, behave yourself.
Mom, let me help you up.
You beast!
Honey, I'm sorry.
I got you such a father.
I'm so sorry.
Mom, it's okay.
I came back this time
to change all of this.
Ma'am, sorry to trouble you.
I will discipline her properly.
It's outrageous.
Keep her in line.
But don't hit her.
Okay.
Give her a good talking.
Ma'am, take care.
I pay to send you to school,
so you can bully others?
You even got recorded!
Even a scumbag like Su Dawei
came blackmail me with that recording.
You've disgraced me completely.
Dad, it was Gu Xiaotang...
You dare argue?
If I hadn't paid to fix this
and bought the recording,
you'd have been expelled by now.
From today on,
all your cards are frozen.
Forget about your allowance.
If you cause any more trouble outside,
I'll break your legs!
One dot.
Red dragon.
I won.
Ms. Lei, you're on a roll today.
Congratulations, Ms. Lei.
What are you waiting for? Pay up.
Are you broke?
You still owe us from last time.
No way.
I... I need to go to the bathroom.
I'll go to the bathroom.
Watch him.
Ms. Lei.
What now?
Ms. Lei,
you must help me get revenge.
It's Gu Xiaotang.
It's all Gu Xiaotang's fault.
It's okay, girl.
Her dad is in our hands.
He can't run.
It's okay.
Continue.
Get him!
Chase him!
Ms. Lei,
he pulls the same trick.
Don't let him get away this time.
Ms. Lei,
you see?
They don't respect you at all.
Since they both don't know the rules,
I'll teach them what the rules are.
Ms. Lei,
this is a distant relative of mine.
He's heard a lot about you,
and wants to follow you.
Could you mentor him?
What's your name?
Ms. Lei, my name is Lu Qingyuan.
♪The face deep in the heart♪
♪Suddenly clear and hazy♪
♪Across time and space, eyes meet again♪
♪Deeply trapped in the vortex♪
♪Searching for familiar outlines♪
♪Persistently guarding,
endlessly cycling♪
♪Even for just a second♪
♪If raindrops flow backward
into the sky♪
♪And sunlight reverses♪
♪As the sun rises and sets,
we reunite with yesterday♪
♪I'll build a dream with you♪
♪Upon the ruins, spring breeze arrives♪
♪Even if there's no end,
I won't regret the start♪
♪Eternity like a day, rushing to you♪
♪You don't need to recognize my eyes♪
♪Following the tracks
of the days that were♪
♪A day like a lifetime, rushing to you♪
♪You don't need to remember my name♪
♪I'll be the dawn you haven't seen♪